Turn off alarm
Get oven glove
Wear oven glove
Open drawer
Get tongs
Open oven
Pull drawer
Pick up tray
Put tray
We're using tongs
Turn using tongs
Turn onion rings
Turn potatoe using tongs
Put tongs
Pick up tray
Open oven
Put tray
Close oven
Set alarm
Open cupboard
Pick up plate
Put plate
Open fridge
Get mayo
Open mayo
Remove something
Remove cover
Open trash bin
Throw cover
Close trash bin
Close mayo
Open mayo
Put mayonnaise onto plate
Squeeze mayonnaise
Close mayonnaise
Open cupboard
Return mayonnaise
Pick up ketchup
Open ketchup
Squeeze ketchup into plate
Close ketchup
Open fridge
Return ketchup
Close fridge
Open drawer
Get spoon
Mix mayonnaise and ketchup in plate
Hold plate and
stir sauce
put plate
[END SUBTITLE]